And on that point,
members of the jury, I rest my case.
(Camera clicks)
(Alarm)
Hello, Wanda.
- Hi, Ken.
- Hello, W-W-Wanda.
Ken... this is Otto.
Hello. Wanda's told me a lot about you.
Hey! Great fish!
A little squeeze of lemon,
some tartare sauce, perfect!
George back yet?
No. He had to g-g-go to the b-b-b...
What?
That's quite a stutter
you've got there, Ken.
It's all right, it doesn't bother me.
So George needs a weapons man, eh?
A cup of tea, Ken?
Y-y-y...
Yeah. He'd like one.
I had a good friend in the CIA
had a stutter. Cost him his life.
(Door opens)
Hi, George.
Hello, George. Get you a Scotch?
Yeah.
George... this is Otto.
So, you're Wanda's brother.
It's good to be here, George.
England is a fine country.
She tell you what we need?
(Ken gasps)
Something like that?
Something like that.
Hello, Wendy.
Had a good day?
I spend the morning trying
to get a waste-disposal man,
have lunch with Marjorie, who kept
complaining about her husband,
then I have to play
three rubbers with Philippa.
And now Sanderson's
have sent the wrong flowers.
Oh, no!
- Would you like some tea?
- Yes.
I won the case.
This is my first moment
of peace all day.
- Hello, Portia. How was the show?
- Awful. I've got to have a new horse
- I thought you liked Phantom.
- He's not fit for dog meat.
- Can I change him? It won't cost much.
- Oughtn't we to ask...
I thought you were making tea, Archie.
I'd better do it.
- Let me do it.
- No, I'll do it!
- I won the case.
- Oh! Now this is cracked.
They're worth about 100,000 each.
There are 135 of them.
That makes 13 millions, my friends.
- Dollars or pounds?
- Pounds, pet.
This is the big one. So...
OK.
Yeah.
Otto?
- Yes?
- OK?
- What?
- The plan.
Yeah. Great. No problem.
What was the middle thing,
about the police?
We don't meet up
at Heathrow until Tuesday...
- Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- I haven't finished yet.
Because the police will watch
all the airports for 72 hours.
I know. I know.
Do you want m-m-me to g-g-get a b-b-big
c-c-car?
Yes, Ken. A limo, OK?
And put diplomatic plates on it, right?
What if he has to speak
in the break-in?
Nobody says anything during
a break-in.
It's OK, Otto. Ken's good.
So next week we won't
have to look for work.
And it won't have to look for us.
Oscar Wilde.
You really like animals, don't you, Ken?
What's the attraction?
Because you can t-t-trust them,
and they don't sh-sh-sh...
- Shit on you?
- Show off all the time.
Know what Nietzsche said about them?
He said they were God's second blunder.
Bye, sis.
Well, you t-tell him from me
that I-I-I...
Bye, George.
If you talk to Mom, tell her I said hi.
- OK.
- (Whispers) Don't let him touch you.
One more day, we're together.
I'm sorry about my brother, Ken.
I know he's insensitive.
He's had a hard life.
Dad used to beat him up.
Good.
- (Man yells)
- (Screaming)
(George) Anybody moves
and you're dead!
(Alarm)
(Dogs yap)
Look where you're going! Chauvinist pig!
Really! People here just think
they own the pavement!
(Engine starts)
(Brakes screech)
That was fun. I love robbing the
English. They're so polite.
- The d-d-d...
- What is it, Ken?
- The dog!
- We didn't hit the dog, Ken. It's OK.
$20 million,
he worried about an insect.
It's not an-an-an...
Stutter's not getting any better, is it?
Shut up!
- Shut up!
- (Siren)
Ken?
Bye.
- Let's split.
- Heathrow, Tuesday.
- Lie low. No celebrating.
- No celebrating?
- See you in a couple of hours.
- OK. Bye.
- To 20 million.
- To a job well done.
To us.
To the best
brother-and-sister team since...
Romeo and Juliet?
Do you believe those cockney klutzes
bought our story? What morons!
- I want you to know something.
- What?
Even if you were my brother,
I'd still want to fuck you.
Oooh!
- Make the call.
- Momento, carissima.
No. No Italian!
Hey!
Per cominciare, due insalate verdi
con peperoni e un linguini primavera.
No. Make the call, Otto.
- Are you really Italian?
- Absolutamente. Si.
My name is Otto. It means eight.
Say "Arrivederci a Giorgio."
- Bye, George.
- (Italian accent) Police, please.
- Otto!
- Argh!
(English accent) Hello.
I thought it might interest you to know
that the Hatton Garden robbery
today was pulled off
by a Mr. George Thomason, who lives at
Flat 3, Kipling Mansions,
Murray Road, London, West 9.
Wanda?
(Siren)
Police! Open up!
Come on, open up!
Open the door, or we'll knock it down.
George Francis Thomason?
Passport, tickets...
...money.
- (Horn)
- (Otto) Asshole!
(Crash)
- We're rich, Wanda.
- Yep?
I bet these last two weeks with me
have been the most exciting
two weeks of your life.
You said it.
(Breathes deeply)
OK.
Disappointed!
Son of a bitch!
What do you have to do in this life
to make people trust you?
Shut up.
People always take advantage of me.
Shut up and think.
Where's he moved it?
- What are you doing?
- I'm thinking!
Thinking what I'll do to him.
First, I'll hang him up
with piano wire...
- Where are you going?
- To talk to him.
Then...
Talk to who? Talk to who?!
So while installing windows
for your parents,
you were kneeling on the floor
where there was broken glass?
- That's right, sir.
- And your parents can confirm this?
Yes. And his aunt, Georgina Thomason.
- Good, Bartlett.
- (Knock at door)
Yes?
Sorry to interrupt you, sir.
- Thomason, lady to see you.
- Anything else?
No. You don't have to
dash off, do you?
No, absolutely not. George?
Ken's got the fish food.
He'll be in later.
- Thanks.
- De nada.
- What do you think?
- We may be all right on the glass.
But what else are they
gonna come up with?
(Wolf whistle)
Oh, George! Oh, my God,
I can't believe this is happening!
That's not allowed in here, miss.
- Are you OK?
- It's all right.
I don't think I can handle this.
I was so afraid
to go to sleep last night, I...
Leave it out. Leave it out, OK?
Now listen, listen, listen, listen.
Listen.
You stayed at my place.
We slept late. You made me breakfast.
What?
- What's he doing here?
- He wanted to see you.
Who did it, George? Kevin Delaney?
Want me to rub him out?
Anything. You name it.
- I have friends making enquiries.
- Good.
The jewels are very safe.
If I get sent down, it all gets
handed back to cut my sentence.
Now, to cut my sentence even more,
I could tell them who done it with me,
if I wasn't very happy about everything.
What was the middle thing?
Piss off.
- You want me to spring you?
- Now!
George?
- You don't think...?
- Do you?
No!
No?
- No.
- OK.
- George?
- What?
Are you sure the garage is very safe?
Trust me.
Thank you very much.
Thanks a lot. Bye. Have a good day.
- So?
- Well, he's not sure it was you.
What about you?
He believes me.
He can't figure out you.
- Figure out what?
- If you turned him in or not, stupid!
Don't, uh, ever, ever,
ever call me stupid. OK?
What?
That's George's lawyer.
The other guy must be the barrister.
- So?
- Trust me.
- Let me know if anything turns up.
- Yes.
Excuse me.
Don't I recognize you?
No. No, I don't think so.
Oh.
But you are
a famous barrister, aren't you?
Er... well, hardly.
Well, could I have
your autograph anyway?
- Yes, yes. Certainly.
- Thanks.
I'm studying aspects of your legal
system. I'm American.
- Oh, really?
- I've just started, though.
It's fascinating.
What, er, what brings you here?
Oh, it's a little embarrassing.
I... have a friend.
Oh! Oh, I see. Well, there you are.
I knew it! You're Archie Leash!
- Leach.
- Right!
I saw you in court. Uh, two weeks ago.
- The casino break-in?
- You were great!
Oh, I'm a big fan of yours.
I love the way you... cross-examine.
- Oh, I really admire your work.
- Thank you.
- I'd better not...
- I don't suppose you...? No. Fine.
Well...
Thank you for this. I'll treasure it.
Au revoir.
You speak French, too.
(Wanda sighs)
What's going on?
Whatever George decides to do,
he's gonna tell Leach first.
- Why?
- Because he's his lawyer.
- Yeah, yeah. I know that.
- So I'm gonna get to know Mr. Leach.
George will tell him
where the diamonds are?
That's what I'm gonna find out.
You done well, my son.
Now, where are we going to hide it?
Very good! Don't tell Wanda anything.
Otto might get something out of her.
- Now...
- George...
You are gonna g-g-get off, aren't you?
Sure, don't worry about it, Ken.
We'll fix it. Now, anything on Otto?
Not yet.
You watch him.
Ken?
OK.
Looks like the police
have been all over it.
Let me just change clothes,
and then I'll help you look.
(English accent)
Hello, K-K-Ken's p-p-pets.
Hey!
Wake up! Wake up, limey fish!
So, how are you gonna
get friendly with this lawyer?
I don't know. I'll improvise.
Fucking insects!
I thought Englishmen didn't like women,
the way they talk.
No. He's straight. He's kinda cute,
too, in a pompous sort of way.
- You got the hots for him?
- I'm not into necrophilia.
(Otto laughs)
What is this,
Hump a Limey Week suddenly?
Otto doesn't approve.
Otto might get jealous.
È molto pericoloso, signorina.
Molto pericolo...
- Carissima.
- Oh, speak it. Speak it!
Un ossobuco milanese con piselli.
Melanzane parmigiana con spinaci.
- Dov'è la farmacia?
- Yes, yes, yes!
- No, no, no.
- Si, si, Si.
No, no, no. No, not here.
- Otto, no.
- Dov'è la Fontana di Trevi?
- Not here, Otto!
- Um...
- Mozzarella.
- No! Not here.
- Parmigiana. Gorgonzola!
- Otto, no!
Eh!
Wanda?
Look what I've got, Wanda.
Treasure!
- (Screams)
- Oh!
Oh, Ken, it's you!
I thought it was the police again.
Isn't it horrible about George? Oh, Ken!
I've such a headache.
Could you pick me up some aspirin?
(Clatter)
- What's that?
- My brother. He's using the bathroom.
- Otto?
- Mm. We just went and saw George.
Oh, it was horrible, Ken.
It was just horrible.
- Wh...
- Isn't it terrible about George?
When I find the bastard who squealed...!
I love that man!
What are you d-d-doing here?
What am I doing here?
Wanda was upset. She needed family.
Sh-sh-she just had a sh-sh-shower.
- I've got to speak to you.
- (Wanda wails)